Start at the TAS Member Gateway: compare editions, watch the tour or enter the free synthetic Demo.
The free Demo is interactive and report-capable, while Professional and Consultant remain protected commercial editions.
Open the Demo. It uses fixed synthetic evidence and never reveals the commercial Golden baseline.
The familiar AURORA command centre is retained: workflow, posture, evidence and outputs remain in one workspace.
Evidence Intake already contains a fixed two-asset synthetic auditpol pack.
Generate Advanced Plus assurance. The Demo runs the full interaction and reporting path against synthetic controls.
The Premium Golden matrix compares assets left-to-right and supports its own scrolling pane.
Select a Golden result row. The matching finding is resolved and the lower detail pane updates automatically.
Use the draggable splitter to give more space to either the matrix or the selected-finding details.
Switch to the raw assurance grid and select any result row.
The lower pane self-populates with status, expected and actual settings, Event IDs, frameworks and remediation.
The top results grid and lower details pane scroll independently, preserving context during investigation.
Open the HTML report preview without leaving the assurance workspace.
Add the detailed evidence report to the browser-local output vault.
The output vault records the generated artefact and offers a direct local download.
Before / After compares fixed current and remediated evidence and highlights improved, regressed and unchanged controls.
The Baseline Library demonstrates searchable control intelligence and Golden comparison structure using synthetic data only.
Event ID Intelligence provides sortable analyst context, collection sources and triage guidance.
Select an event to populate its analyst detail pane.
Return to the Member Gateway to review licensing, verified hashes and the protected installer journey.
The real x64 TAS v10.0.6 MSI is staged and hash-verified, but the public site never exposes it directly.
A valid Professional or Consultant entitlement unlocks the protected download; the installed app then validates the signed licence and machine binding.
TAS turns raw Windows audit evidence into defensible security assurance—free to explore, licensed for real customer evidence.